eons.com 2012-05-15

# Privacy Policy | eons.com

## EONS.COM PRIVACY POLICY

### Introduction and Scope

We at Eons want you to feel safe online. For that reason, we follow a privacy policy that applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Crew Media, LLC, or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. In line with that policy, we want to let you know how we treat user data that we collect and receive from [Eons](http://www.eons.com/).

The term, “Eons,” as used in this Privacy Policy, refers to either the Eons Website, Eons.com, or Crew Media, LLC. Personal information is defined as information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address or phone number; this information is generally referred to online as Personal Identifying Information, or "PII".

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other data, including, without limitation, data that we collect offline or data that others collect on websites that are linked to the Site.

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers the following: 

Eons’ Privacy Policy applies only to websites and services that are owned and operated by Crew Media, LLC. While other websites may be displayed as search results or links from within Eons, those sites are owned and operated by others, and they may have different privacy policies. When linking from Eons to other websites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites.

#### Personal Identifying Information and User Generated Content

**It’s also important to note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you post, yourself, in public areas of the Eons Website.** For example, if you choose to let other people see your name, your profile, and any Personal Identifying Information provided as answers to other Profile questions – or if you post information or comments on a discussion board, that information will be made public. Your messages and other information you make available in public areas of the Eons Website will be seen by people and organizations not related to or controlled by Eons, and may be used by others to contact you.

#### Credentials – Screen Names & Passwords

Each Registered Member and Registered Partner HQ Member is encouraged to create an identifying screen name (if a screen name is not created, a user's first name and last name initial is used instead) and is required to create a password that will be the main credential used to access their account on the Website. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and other account details, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You may change your password at any time by updating your account settings on the Eons Website. You can also change your screen name **once** under your account settings. You agree to immediately notify Eons of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. Eons cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this section.

#### Security

We take reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. But, you should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free.

### Types of Data Collected and Use

You actively send information to us when you sign up with us a member on a Site, participate in surveys or promotions, post topics in Eons groups, respond to us or otherwise contact us. Depending on your choices, you may send us personally identifiable information such as your email address, name, mailing address, phone number, birthday, and gender; password; baby due date/birthday, name and gender. But, you can also use certain features of our Sites without telling us your name and if you do not tell us who you are, we do not try to find out.

We also track information about how our Site is used by you through cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs). For example, your Internet browser automatically transmits to us information such as the URL of the website you just came from and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using. In addition, we participate in ad networks. The ad networks that we participate in collect anonymous information using cookies to target some of the advertising you see on the Sites and on other third party websites.

You can set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse or delete cookies altogether, but certain features of the Sites might not work without certain cookies. If you have actively sent us your name or other personally identifiable information, we may combine such information with tracked information for the purposes set forth below.

### Purposes of Data Collection

We collect information about you because we want to determine what you may like or find interesting, so we can provide you with targeted information and advertising (on our Site, in newsletters, via email and otherwise). In addition, we use data to create statistics and reports where personally identifiable information has been removed and aggregated (such that it is anonymous as regards any specific user) for various business purposes such as research products for example, to support the Site.

### User Data Sharing and Disclosure

Member Profile information is displayed to people in order to facilitate member interaction in the Eons social networking community.

We keep your personally identifiable information confidential and we generally do not disclose it. But, please note the following clarifications and exceptions:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Eons under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your user data to help Eons communicate with you about offers from Eons and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We may sometimes share aggregate non-user data with third parties such as the media, advertisers and government agencies. This aggregate information is typically in the form of statistics, such as numbers of Eons members who live in a particular state or fall within a particular age group. Such aggregate information is gathered from individual Eons members’ information but is not traceable to any specific identifiable Eons member.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Eons terms of use or as otherwise required or permitted by law.
  * If Eons is acquired by or merged with or into another company, we may transfer your user data to the new owner, so the services you receive from Eons can continue without interruption. If any such transfer of information, your user data would remain subject to the Eons Privacy Policy in place at that time. As is the case now, however, the Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so it's important that you review these pages regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current Privacy Policy.

#### Our Advertisers

We do not share your user data with our advertisers. The advertising we display, however, is targeted to users of particular services and content. So if you view or click on a targeted ad, the advertiser (or other companies affiliated with the advertiser) may assume that you meet the targeting criteria, for example, women ages 50-60 from a particular geographic area or with children or grandchildren of a certain age.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Eons, like many websites, uses cookies to prepare customized Web pages for you. A cookie is a file containing a string of code that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive, to be kept there for later use. With cookies in place, whenever you use your Web browser (such as Internet Explorer, AOL or Mozilla Firefox) to connect to Eons, our systems are able to recognize you. This enables Eons to present you with custom Web pages. So, for example, instead of seeing just a generic welcome page, you see a welcome page with your name on it and information that relates to where you live (your ZIP code) and products or services that reflect your interests.

In addition to Eons’ cookies, when you visit Eons your computer may receive cookies from our advertisers and from other sites displayed as search results or links. The cookies inserted by those third parties are not covered by Eons’ Privacy Policy, but rather, by the policies of those advertisers and outside websites.

You can set up your browser to reject cookies or tell you when a cookie has been sent. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of Eons’ interactive features, and we hope you will leave them turned on.

Eons also uses web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs) to access Eons cookies inside and outside our Web pages and in connection with Eons products and services. A web beacon is a transparent image placed on a web page that sends a signal when a person visits that page. This enables us to assess the popularity and effectiveness of the material posted on the Eons Website. We may also use web beacons in connection with e-mails sent to Eons members, to let us know whether and when the e-mail was opened. No user data is transmitted through web beacons.

#### Third-party Ad Serving

Eons contracts with third party companies to help us make sure that our content and advertising are relevant and effective, and to analyze how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The type of information we collect includes, for example, the pages you visited at Eons. This information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which products are most interesting and what kinds of offers our visitors like to see. Although our third party marketing partners manage the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy, you can “opt-out” of allowing us to analyze such data by [clicking here](http://www.omniture.com/privacy/policy#optout).

  * The ads on Eons pages are delivered to you by AARP Media, our web advertising partner. Information about your visit to Eons, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, is used to serve new or increasingly relevant ads to you whenever you visit Eons. For more information about AARP Media, please visit advertise.aarp.org. For any issues you believe are related to advertisements, to report inappropriate or questionable advertisements, or if you have further questions about how Eons and AARP Media utilize user data, please contact Eons at [ EonsHelp@eons.com ](mailto:%20eonshelp@eons.com)
  * Eons utilizes third party advertising companies to serve a portion of the ads on the site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our site in order to provide relevant offers. You can find out more information about this practice and your choices concerning this practice at <http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

### Updating Your Account Information & Preferences

You can update your Eons Account Information, including your biographical and Profile information, at any time, by going to the [Account Settings ](https://www.eons.com/accounts/myaccount) page and editing your [profile](http://www.eons.com/members/profile).

  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Notifications settings page from time to time. Members who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain important communications relating to the Eons service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, throughout the term of your personal Eons account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving these important communications. 

#### Deactivating Your Eons Account Membership

To leave Eons and cancel your membership altogether, once you're logged in, you can deactivate your account from your [Accounts Settings](https://www.eons.com/accounts/myaccount) page.

Deactivation will prevent you from logging in to Eons, remove your Profile, remove any connections you have made (Friends, Groups, etc.) and you will no longer receive emails from Eons or its members. 

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be changed periodically. We will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Eons account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Please do return to review this policy occasionally for any minor updates implemented and not otherwise announced.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, please email us at [info@eons.com](http://www.eons.com/about/contact) or you can contact us at: 

> Crew Media, LLC  
>  2220 Powell Street, Suite 515  
>  Emeryville, CA 94608

**Effective Date: January 26, 2012**
